<resources>
  <string name="app_name">ZamVoyage</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="title_home">Home</string>
  <string name="title_search">Search</string>
  <string name="title_plan">Plan a Trip</string>
  <string name="title_explore">Explore</string>
  <string name="empty_string"></string>
  <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>

  <!-- History -->
  <string name="history_paragraph_1">The evolution of the name “Zamboanga” provides an interesting insight into its historical background. The early Malay settlers called the region “Jambangan”, which means Land of the Flowers.</string>

  <string name="history_paragraph_2">These Malays who built their settlements by the river banks were the subanons, which is the “People of the River”. Later on, Badjaos who came on their frail vintas also settled here, built their frail huts along the shorelines and confused “Jambangan” with “Samboangan” which comes from the word “Sabuan”, the wooden pole used to help push their vintas in shallow waters or to tie them for anchorage purposes. </string>

  <string name="history_paragraph_3">The Spanish colonizers found difficulty in pronouncing “Samboangan” and instead called the place “Zamboanga”.</string>

  <string name="history_paragraph_4">The city has rich and colorful history. It was the center of barter trading among Chinese, Malays and the native Tausugs, Samals, Subanons, and the Badjaos as early as the 13th and 14th centuries. It was in 1569 when the Spaniards made their presence felt with a small Catholic Mission established briefly at La Caldera, now known as Recodo. Much later on June 23, 1635, the cornerstone of what is now known as Fort Pilar was laid by Father Melchor de Vera, a Jesuit Priest-Engineer and the Spanish authorities. This date marked the change of the name of the place from Samboangan to Zamboanga. It is the city’s founding date.</string>

  <string name="history_paragraph_5">Zamboanga is also often called as "Asia's Latin City", partly because the Chavacano language, a Spanish-based creole, is common and partly because it shares other Spanish traditions; it even has the same patron saint as Spain, Our Lady of the Pilar. </string>

  <string name="history_paragraph_6">In 1899, immediately after the Spanish-American War in the Philippines, the United States of America established full authority in Zamboanga. A special form of government was established in Mindanao and Sulu. Zamboanga was made the capital. The first form of which was the Moro province and during the 12 years of its existence, the American Military Government in the Philippines converted Zamboanga into a city in the Commission Form, the first province of Mindanao to become a city.</string>

  <!-- Attractions Content -->
  <string name="great_santa_cruz_island_paragraph_1">Also known as “Pink Beach”, is a popular tourist destination located off the coast of Zamboanga City, Philippines. The island is famous for its stunning pink sand beach, which is created by the presence of red organ-pipe coral fragments mixed with white sand. The crystal-clear waters are perfect for swimming, while the coral reefs are home to a variety of marine life, making it an ideal spot for snorkeling. Island hopping is also a popular activity, as visitors can explore the nearby islands and their beautiful beaches. </string>

  <string name="great_santa_cruz_island_paragraph_2">To visit the island, there is an entrance fee which includes a boat ride to and from the island. The boat ride offers stunning views of the sea, making it a great way to start the island adventure. Once on the island, visitors can take advantage of several facilities including restrooms, picnic areas, and a small restaurant that serves up local cuisine. </string>

  <string name="once_islas_paragraph_1">Once Islas is a nature reserve that became an ecotourism spot back in 2018 in an effort to showcase the beauty of its islands and provide livelihood for its locals. A steadily rising tourist attraction is Once Islas(11 Islands), a string of islands and islets off the eastern coast of Zamboanga City. There are designated snorkeling spots for those who want to take a peek into the underwater scene. Buh-Buh, Bisaya-Bisaya, Baung-Baung, and Sirommon are those that are accessible to the public. It is a popular destination for tourists who want to experience the beauty of nature. The islands are known for their crystal-clear waters and white sandy beaches, making them perfect for swimming, snorkeling, and diving. Visitors can also explore the islands\' lush forests and discover various species of flora and fauna.</string>

  <string name="lantawan_grassland_paragraph_1">It is a mountain located in Lantawan, Pasonanca. The mountain is covered in lush grasslands and is home to a wide variety of flora and fauna. Visitors to Lantawan Grassland can enjoy a wide range of activities, including hiking, camping, and birdwatching. The surrounding area is also home to several hiking trails, which provide stunning views of the mountain and the surrounding jungle. Climbing to the top of Lantawan Grassland is a challenging but rewarding experience, and the views from the summit are truly unforgettable. If you\'re interested in visiting Lantawan Grassland, it\'s best to hire a local guide to help you navigate the mountain.</string>

  <string name="merloquet_falls_paragraph_1"> It is a stunning waterfall that is located in Barangay Sibulao, Zamboanga City, Philippines. The waterfall is situated in a lush jungle setting, surrounded by towering cliffs and dense vegetation. Merloquet Falls is a multi-tiered waterfall that cascades down into a crystal-clear pool, which is perfect for swimming and relaxing. The falls are fed by a natural spring, which provides a continuous flow of cool, refreshing water. Visitors to Merloquet Falls can enjoy a wide range of activities, including swimming, hiking, and picnicking. The surrounding area is home to several hiking trails, which provide stunning views of the waterfall and the surrounding jungle. </string>

  <string name="merloquet_falls_paragraph_2"> Merloquet Falls is also home to several species of wildlife, including birds, butterflies, and monkeys. Visitors to the falls can often spot these animals in their natural habitat, adding to the unique and unforgettable experience of visiting Merloquet Falls. There is a small entrance fee to visit Merloquet Falls, which is used to maintain the surrounding area and ensure that it remains a beautiful and pristine destination for visitors to enjoy. The entrance fee is typically around 20 to 30 pesos per person, which is a small price to pay for the unforgettable experience of visiting this stunning waterfall. </string>

  <string name="the_fort_pilar_shrine_and_museum_paragraph_1"> It is a popular landmark in Zamboanga City that is steeped in history and culture. The fort was built by the Spanish in the 17th century to protect against pirates and other invaders, and now serves as a museum and a shrine to the patron saint of Zamboanga. The museum houses a collection of artifacts and exhibits that showcase the history and culture of the city, as well as the fort\'s role in the country\'s struggle for independence.</string>

  <string name="the_fort_pilar_shrine_and_museum_paragraph_2"> The shrine is also a popular place of pilgrimage for Catholics, who come to pray to the Lady of the Pillar, the patron saint of Zamboanga. The fort is open to visitors daily, and admission is free. If you\'re interested in history and culture, the Fort Pilar Shrine and Museum is definitely worth a visit.</string>

  <string name="the_metropolitan_cathedral_of_the_immaculate_conception_paragraph_1"> It is one of the oldest and most beautiful churches in Zamboanga City. It is the seat of the Archdiocese of Zamboanga and is located in the heart of the city. The cathedral was built in the late 19th century and features an impressive Gothic Revival architecture, with beautiful stained-glass windows and intricate carvings. </string>

  <string name="the_metropolitan_cathedral_of_the_immaculate_conception_paragraph_2"> The cathedral is a popular place of worship for Catholics in the city, and it is also a popular tourist destination. Visitors can attend mass, admire the architecture, or simply enjoy the peaceful and serene atmosphere. If you\'re interested in history, culture, or religion, the Metropolitan Cathedral of the Immaculate Conception is definitely worth a visit. </string>

  <string name="the_zamboanga_city_hall_paragraph_1"> The center government of the city. It is located in the heart of the city and features beautiful neoclassical architecture. The building was constructed in the early 20th century and has since been renovated and expanded. The Zamboanga City Hall houses the offices of the city\'s mayor, vice mayor, and councilors, as well as other government agencies and departments. Visitors can tour the building and admire its architecture, and they can also attend public meetings and events. The Zamboanga City Hall is an important landmark in the city and is a great place to learn about the local government and its role in the community. </string>

  <string name="the_pasonanca_park_paragraph_1"> It is a popular tourist attraction located in Zamboanga City, Philippines. There is no entrance fee to visit the tree house, but visitors are encouraged to make a donation to help maintain the park. The park is open daily from 6 AM to 7 PM. In addition to the tree house, the Pasonanca Park also features a variety of other attractions, including a swimming pool, picnic areas, and hiking trails. Visitors can also explore the nearby waterfalls and natural pools. The Pasonanca Tree House is a unique and interesting place to visit, as it offers a stunning view of the surrounding forest and the city. </string>

  <string name="the_pasonanca_park_paragraph_2"> Constructed in 1960, it was originally built to serve as the Youth Citizenship Training Center. Today, visitors come here to take photos, but if you want to spend more time here, you can rent the treehouse too! Make sure to contact the LGU’s admin first to coordinate. You can buy food along the way from the sidestreet restaurants, stores, and BBQ stands.</string>

  <string name="paseo_del_mar_paragraph_1"> It is a waterfront park that offers a variety of activities and attractions for visitors of all ages. The park is open daily from 6 AM to 10 PM. The park features a variety of attractions, including a playground, a skating rink, and a food court. Visitors can also enjoy a stroll along the waterfront promenade, which offers stunning views of the nearby islands. The park is also home to a variety of events and festivals throughout the year, including the Zamboanga Hermosa Festival. In addition to the attractions, Paseo del Mar is also home to a variety of restaurants and food stalls, serving up a variety of local and international cuisine. Visitors can enjoy a meal while taking in the beautiful views of the sea and the nearby islands. </string>

  <!-- Activities Content -->

  <string name="hermosa_festival_paragraph_1"> One of the most popular cultural events in Zamboanga City. It is celebrated every October in honor of the city\'s patron saint, Nuestra Señora del Pilar. The festival is a week-long celebration that features a variety of cultural performances, including traditional dances, music, and street parades. One of the highlights of the festival is the "Vinta" parade, which features colorful boats that are decorated with flowers and other ornaments. The boats are modeled after the traditional boats used by the Badjao people, who are indigenous to the region. Another popular event is the "Zambolympics," which is a series of sporting events that are held throughout the city. The events include basketball, volleyball, and other traditional sports, as well as unique events like "sack races" and "tug-of-war." The Hermosa Festival also features a variety of food and craft fairs, where visitors can sample local delicacies and purchase souvenirs and gifts. The festival is a great way to experience the local culture and to celebrate the city\'s rich history and traditions. If you\'re interested in culture and the arts, the Hermosa Festival is definitely worth checking out! </string>

  <string name="the_regatta_de_zamboanga_paragraph_1"> A popular annual boat race that takes place in Zamboanga City, Philippines. It is typically held in March and is one of the most colorful and exciting events in the city. The race features a variety of boats, including traditional vintas and modern sailboats, which are decorated with colorful flags and other ornaments. The boats race along a course that runs along the coast of Zamboanga City, providing a beautiful backdrop for the race. The Regatta de Zamboanga is a great way to experience the local culture and to celebrate the city\'s rich maritime heritage. It is also a fun and exciting event that is enjoyed by locals and tourists alike. </string>

  <string name="zamboanga_city_bird_festival_paragraph_1"> Considered as the country’s biggest celebration of avifaunal diversity, Zamboanga City Bird Festival is celebrated by birdwatchers, conservationists, and tourists from local and foreign origins. Zamboanga is not only rich in endemic birdlife but also attractive for migratory birds since it provides a suitable ecosystem for a myriad of bird species. The coastal wetlands of Zamboanga are inviting to congregations of migratory terns and wader species such as stilts, sandpipers, and plovers. The fishponds around serve as nesting areas for black-crowned herons, rufous, and great egrets. As you ascend high altitudes, you may catch a glimpse of more elusive species like Steere’s pitta and writhed hornbill. During this Zamboanga peninsula tradition, participants of all ages parade in colorful bird costumes. You can take beautiful photos of the vivid colors and the smiles of many as they parade down the streets of Zamboanga City. Locals also showcase their cuisine to help boost tourism in the region.</string>

  <string name="flores_de_mayo_paragraph_1"> “Flowers of May” is the direct translation of this festival’s Spanish name. It is a monthlong revelry that is held during May annually, and it is celebrated in honor of the Virgin Mary. Unlike bougainvilleas that bloom year-round, there are a number of flowers that bloom only in the month of May, which include hibiscus, Chichiricas, and caballero. During this festival, flower offerings are made daily in churches and village chapels inside barrios. The traditional procession is highlighted by statues of the Virgin Mary in colorful floral decorations. The festival culminates at the end of May with Santacruzan, a daylong celebration of parades and processions. It is a ritual pageant that depicts the discovery of the true cross by Queen Helena, the mother of Constantine the Great. Participants from different places in the Philippines visit the city to take part during Flores de Mayo. The representatives wear beautiful national Filipino attires as they walk down the streets of Zamboanga. </string>

  <string name="dia_de_zamboanga_paragraph_1"> It is the biggest festival in Zamboanga City and is celebrated annually on February 26. The festival is a celebration of the city\'s founding and its rich cultural heritage. It is a week-long celebration that showcases the city\'s unique culture and traditions. The festival features a variety of events, including a grand parade, cultural shows, beauty pageants, sports competitions, and food fairs. The festival also includes a street dance competition where participants wear colorful costumes and perform traditional dances. Another highlight of the festival is the "Zamboanga Hermosa" beauty pageant, which is open to young women from all over the city. The pageant aims to promote the city\'s beauty and talent and to showcase the women\'s intelligence, poise, and grace. The festival is a great opportunity for visitors to experience the city\'s vibrant culture and to learn more about its rich history and traditions. The festival is also an opportunity for the city to showcase its unique culture, traditions, and local products. During the festival, the city comes alive with colorful decorations, parades, and performances. The event attracts both locals and tourists alike, making it a fun and exciting time to visit Zamboanga City.</string>

  <!-- Amenities Content -->
  <string name="satti_paragraph_1"> This popular breakfast dish consists of grilled meat on a stick, usually chicken or beef, served with rice cakes and a spicy sauce made with chili, garlic, and vinegar. The meat is marinated in a mixture of spices and coconut milk, giving it a rich and savory flavor. There are many Satti Houses in Zamboanga City, but most recommended is Jimmy’s Satti Haus along Pilar Street. </string>

  <string name="alavar_seafood_restaurant_paragraph_1"> It is a popular seafood restaurant located in the heart of Zamboanga City. The restaurant is known for its delicious seafood dishes, particularly its famous curacha dish. The restaurant has a cozy and welcoming atmosphere, making it a great place to enjoy a meal with friends and family. Alavar Seafood Restaurant is located on Don Alfaro Street, which is a bustling commercial district with many shops and businesses. </string>

  <string name="alavar_seafood_restaurant_paragraph_2"> The restaurant is open from 10:00 AM to 8:00 PM. They offer dine-in, takeout, and delivery services. The restaurant uses fresh ingredients to create their dishes, which are cooked to perfection. Their signature dish is the curacha, a type of crab that is native to the waters of Zamboanga City. The curacha is cooked in a special sauce made from coconut milk and other secret ingredients, giving it a unique and delicious flavor. </string>

  <string name="bay_tal_mal_restaurant_paragraph_1"> It is a Filipino restaurant located at Mayor Jaldon St, Canelar, Zamboanga City, Zamboanga Sibugay Province. The restaurant offers a variety of Filipino dishes such as adobo, sinigang, and kare-kare. It might be worth checking out if you\'re in the area and looking for some Filipino food. Bay Tal Mal Restaurant is open from 9:00 AM to 9:00 PM. They offer dine-in, takeout, and delivery services. The restaurant has a simple and cozy atmosphere, making it a great place to enjoy a meal with friends and family. They also offer catering services for special events. The restaurant is a bustling commercial district with many shops and businesses. If you\'re in the area and looking for some delicious Filipino food, Bay Tal Mal Restaurant is definitely worth a visit. </string>

  <string name="brews_almighty_paragraph_1"> It is a cozy cafe located in Zamboanga City. The cafe serves a variety of coffee drinks, such as espresso, latte, cappuccino, and cold brew. They also have a selection of teas and other beverages. For food, they offer sandwiches, pastries, and cakes. The cafe has indoor and outdoor seating, and is located near Paseo del Mar, making it a great place to relax and enjoy the view. The cafe has a laid-back and friendly atmosphere and is popular among locals and tourists alike. The coffee drinks prices range from PHP 100 to PHP 200 (around $2 to $4 USD), while their sandwiches and pastries range from PHP 100 to PHP 250 (around $2 to $5 USD). The prices may vary depending on the type of drink or food you order. </string>

  <string name="canelar_barter_trade_center_paragraph_1"> Canelar Barter Trade Center is an Arts and Crafts Store located in Barangay Canelar, Zamboanga, Zamboanga Peninsula. It is a great place to find unique and handmade items, such as woven baskets, textiles, and wood carvings. The store is known for its affordable prices and friendly vendors, who are always happy to help customers find what they\'re looking for. The store is open daily from morning to evening, so you can visit at your convenience.</string>

  <string name="canelar_barter_trade_center_paragraph_2"> It is a popular destination for tourists and locals alike. The store is located in a bustling commercial district, so it\'s easily accessible by public transportation. The items sold at the store are unique and handmade, so you won\'t find them anywhere else. The vendors are known for their hospitality, and many of them are willing to negotiate prices, making it a great place to find souvenirs and gifts. In addition to arts and crafts, Canelar Barter Trade Center also offers a variety of food and drinks, including local delicacies and refreshing beverages. </string>

  <string name="chikalang_paragraph_1"> It is a snack food in bilao or packed in plastic usually sold by street vendors in Zamboanga city. It is a local delicacy that is made from glutinous rice shaped like a twisted donut or pinilipit. It is fried and coated with flour and caramelized sugar. It is available at Vista del Mar Beach Resort that is sold for 90 pesos per plate of 8-10 pieces. </string>

  <string name="curacha_paragraph_1"> Curacha got its name because of its spiky, hairy appearance that kinda resembles you-know-what. But if you look closely, it kinda appears like the love child of a wide crab and a long lobster. And because it packs more meat and more flavor than the crabs we’re used to, they are sought after. Thankfully, they thrive in the waters surrounding the region. For many, the best place to have a taste of curacha is Alavar Seafood Restaurant, which serves curacha cooked in and doused with its famous specialty sauce, which is made from coconut milk, aligue (crab roe paste) and various spices. This super rich sauce combined with the seafood umami bombs that are curacha, you’ll never taste other crab dishes the same way again.</string>

  <string name="holy_smokes_korean_grill_and_resto_paragraph_1"> It is an Asian restaurant located at 166 Cabato Road, 2F Blue Gym Building, Zamboanga City, Zamboanga Sibugay Province. They offer a variety of Korean dishes such as bulgogi, bibimbap, and Korean fried chicken. The restaurant is known for its delicious food, friendly staff, and cozy atmosphere. The prices are also very reasonable, making it a great place to enjoy Korean food without breaking the bank. They serve dinner and lunch meals such as Asian, Korean, Grill barbecue and soups. It available for delivery, takeout, seating, bars, and they accept digital payments or cash.</string>

  <string name="kape_zambo_acoustic_bar_and_restaurant_paragraph_1"> It is an Asian restaurant located on Canelar St, Fronting Metrobank, Zamboanga City, Zamboanga Sibugay Province. The restaurant is known for its acoustic music and great food. They offer a variety of dishes, including Filipino and Asian cuisine. Prices are reasonable, making it a great place to enjoy a meal with friends and family. It is open from 11:00 AM to 11:00 PM. </string>

  <string name="kape_zambo_acoustic_bar_and_restaurant_paragraph_2"> They have a cozy and welcoming atmosphere, making it a great place to hang out with friends and enjoy some live music. The restaurant is located in a bustling commercial district, so it\'s easily accessible by public transportation. They offer dine-in, takeout, and delivery services, so you can enjoy their delicious food no matter where you are. In addition to their food and music, Kape Zambo Acoustic Bar and Restaurant also offers a variety of drinks, including coffee, tea, and alcoholic beverages. </string>

  <string name="kcc_mall_de_zamboanga_paragraph_1"> KCC Mall de Zamboanga is a large shopping mall located in Barangay Canelar, Zamboanga City. This mall is one of the biggest malls in Zamboanga City. Parking is available for free, and there are plenty of restrooms throughout the mall. It\'s a popular destination for shopping, dining, and entertainment. The mall features a wide variety of stores, including clothing, electronics, and home goods. It also has a large supermarket and a cinema complex, which features multiple screens showing the latest movies. The mall also has a grocery store and a department store. The mall is known for its spacious and clean facilities, as well as its friendly staff. If you\'re looking for a one-stop-shop for all your shopping and entertainment needs, KCC Mall de Zamboanga is definitely worth checking out.</string>

  <string name="knickerbocker_paragraph_1"> Think of it as the fruitier, healthier stepsister of the halo-halo. This crazy colorful concoction is a mix of jellies and fresh fruits like watermelon, apple, pineapple, and mango, drizzled with condensed milk and topped with shaved ice and strawberry ice cream. It’s bright, sweet, and creamy, perfect for washing down whatever lunch or dinner you had. </string>

  <string name="knickerbocker_paragraph_2"> These days, you can enjoy a cup from vendors at Paseo del Mar, but if you’re after the original, head over to Hacienda de Palmeras Hotel and Restaurant for only Php 65, widely regarded as the establishment that invented this tropical dessert. The restaurant is set in a garden in a quiet corner of the city, but still easily accessible by jeepney or tricycle.</string>

  <string name="lokot_lokot_paragraph_1"> A local delicacy found in Zamboanga city and other parts of Mindanao. It is called by the locals as “jaa”, “lokot-lokot”, “Zambo Rolls, or “tagktak”, depending on where you find the delicacy. This crunchy dessert that is made from rice flour, sugar, oil, and water is one of the popular pasalubong to bring back home after a visit from Zamboanga City. </string>

  <string name="yakan_weaving_center_paragraph_1"> It is a cultural center located in Barangay Upper Calarian, Zamboanga City. The center is dedicated to preserving and promoting the traditional art of Yakan weaving. The Yakan people are known for their intricate and colorful textiles, which are made using traditional weaving techniques. Yakan weaving is a traditional art form that has been passed down from generation to generation, and the Yakan Weaving Center is dedicated to preserving this cultural heritage. </string>

  <string name="yakan_weaving_center_paragraph_2"> The center also provides training and employment opportunities for local weavers, helping to support the local economy. At the center, visitors can watch weavers at work and learn about the history and significance of Yakan weaving. The center also has a gift shop where visitors can purchase handmade Yakan textiles, such as blankets, shawls, and bags. The Yakan Weaving Center is open daily from morning to evening, and admission is free. The center is located in a quiet and peaceful area, so it\'s a great place to escape the hustle and bustle of the city. </string>

  <!-- Accommodations Content -->
  <string name="casa_canelar_pension_paragraph_1"> It is a cozy hotel located in the heart of Zamboanga City. The hotel offers comfortable rooms that are equipped with air conditioning, a flat-screen TV, and a private bathroom. Some rooms also come with a seating area and a balcony. The hotel has a 24-hour front desk, free Wi-Fi, and a restaurant that serves a variety of local and international dishes. The price range for a room at Casa Canelar Pension is around 1,500 PHP to 2,500 PHP per night, depending on the room type and season. </string>

  <string name="casa_canelar_pension_paragraph_2"> Breakfast is included in the room rate. It is located in a convenient location in the city, close to several shopping malls, restaurants, and tourist attractions. The hotel offers a variety of services to its guests, including room service, laundry, and airport shuttle. The hotel also has a conference room that can accommodate up to 50 people, making it a good option for business travelers. The hotel staff is friendly and accommodating, and they can assist guests with arranging tours and transportation around the city. </string>

  <string name="garden_orchid_hotel_paragraph_1"> It is a luxurious hotel located in Governor Camins Avenue, Zamboanga City. The hotel offers a variety of rooms, ranging from deluxe rooms to suites, with rates starting at around PHP 4,000 per night. Each room is equipped with air conditioning, flat-screen TVs, and free Wi-Fi. The hotel also features several dining options, including a restaurant serving local and international cuisine, a cafe, and a bar. Other amenities include an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a spa. The hotel also offers meeting and event facilities. </string>

  <string name="grand_astoria_hotel_paragraph_1"> It is another popular hotel located in Mayor Jaldon Street, Zamboanga City. The hotel offers a variety of rooms, ranging from deluxe rooms to suites, with rates starting at around PHP 3,000 per night. Each room is equipped with air conditioning, flat-screen TVs, and free Wi-Fi. The hotel also features several dining options, including a restaurant serving local and international cuisine, a cafe, and a bar. Other amenities include an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a spa. The hotel also offers meeting and event facilities. </string>

  <string name="hamilton_business_inn_paragraph_1">It is a modern hotel located in the heart of Zamboanga City. The hotel offers comfortable rooms that are equipped with air conditioning, a flat-screen TV, and a private bathroom. Some rooms also come with a seating area and a balcony. The hotel has a 24-hour front desk, free Wi-Fi, and a restaurant that serves a variety of local and international dishes. The price range for a room at Hamilton Business Inn is around 1,500 PHP to 2,500 PHP per night, depending on the room type and season. Breakfast is included in the room rate. The hotel offers a variety of services to its guests, including room service, laundry, and airport shuttle. The hotel also has a conference room that can accommodate up to 100 people, making it a good option for business travelers. </string>

  <string name="lantaka_hotel_by_the_sea_paragraph_1"> It is a beautiful hotel located in Valderosa Street, Zamboanga City. The hotel offers a variety of rooms, ranging from deluxe rooms to suites, with rates starting at around PHP 3,000 per night. Each room is equipped with air conditioning, flat-screen TVs, and free Wi-Fi. The hotel also features several dining options, including a restaurant serving local and international cuisine, a cafe, and a bar. The hotel is situated right by the sea, providing guests with stunning views of the water. Other amenities include an outdoor pool, a fitness center, and a spa. The hotel also offers meeting and event facilities. </string>

  <string name="zamboanga_town_home_bed_and_breakfast_1">It is conveniently located in the popular City Proper area. The hotel has everything you need for a comfortable stay. Service-minded staff will welcome and guide you at the Zamboanga Town Home Bed and Breakfast. Guestrooms are designed to provide an optimal level of comfort with welcoming decor and some offering convenient amenities like television LCD/plasma screen, internet access – wireless, internet access – wireless (complimentary), non-smoking rooms, air conditioning. The hotel offers various recreational opportunities with price ranges 1500-2500 per night. A welcoming atmosphere and excellent service are what you can expect during your stay at Zamboanga Town Home Bed and Breakfast. The establishment is near the center of the city which is just one jeepney ride away or a tricycle </string>

  <!-- Accessibilities Content -->
  <string name="bus_terminals_paragraph_1"> The terminal has several bus bays and ticketing counters. The terminal serves several bus companies that operate routes to other cities in Mindanao, including Dapitan, Dipolog, Pagadian, and Cotabato. It is also conveniently located near other transportation hubs such as the city\'s seaport and airport, making it easy for travelers to connect to other modes of transportation. </string>

  <string name="taxi_paragraph_1"> Most taxis are equipped with air conditioning, and many have a small screen displaying the fare and distance traveled. Taxis are required to have a meter that calculates the fare based on the distance traveled and time spent in traffic. Passengers can pay for their ride in cash or, in some cases, using a credit card. </string>
  
  <string name="tricycle_paragraph_1"> The fare for a tricycle ride is usually negotiated with the driver, and it\'s important to agree on the fare before starting the ride. Tricycles can be found throughout the city, and they are often used to access areas that are not accessible by larger vehicles. </string>
  
  <string name="zamboanga_international_airport_paragraph_1"> The airport serves the Zamboanga Peninsula region and is a hub for several airlines, including Cebu Pacific, Philippine Airlines, and AirAsia. The airport has a single terminal building and offers both domestic and international flights, with destinations including Manila, Cebu, Davao, and Kota Kinabalu. </string>
  
  <string name="zamboanga_international_seaport_paragraph_1"> The seaport is one of the busiest in the region and serves as a gateway to nearby destinations such as Basilan, Jolo, and Tawi-Tawi. Seaport is equipped with modern facilities such as cranes, cargo-handling equipment, and storage facilities to handle different types of cargo. It also has a passenger terminal that offers comfortable waiting areas, restrooms, and other amenities for travelers. </string>
  
  <string name="zamboanga_motor_rental_paragraph_1"> A company in Zamboanga City offer a range of motorcycles and scooters for rent, including small and large motorcycles, automatic and manual scooters, and dirt bikes. Rental periods can range from a few hours to several days or weeks, and rental plans include daily, weekly, and monthly rentals with price range starting at P1500. </string>
  
</resources>
